freshsofts.com 2015-12-21

# Privacy Policy : Freshsofts.com

**Your Information**

Privacy policy of Freshsofts.com covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by Freshsofts.com anytime you interact with us such as when you make a purchase, contact a technical support or sales associate, sign up for an e-newsletter or request a download of demonstration software.

We collect your personal information because it assists us in delivering a high level of customer service. For example, your personal information helps us to keep you informed and up-to-date on the latest product updates and announcements as well as special offers that may be extended from time to time.

When you provide Freshsofts.com with your name, email address, mailing address or telephone number, and you do not “opt-out”, Freshsofts.com and our customer representatives and authorized affiliates may use the provided information to alert you to product updates, special offers, updated information, new products and other information. Other than our representatives and authorized affiliates (such as value-added resellers), Freshsofts.com does not offer, sell, or otherwise make available any user-provided information to third parties.

Freshsofts.com will send notifications regarding product updates and technical support notices. These messages are deemed essential to the functionality of your product and as such, there is no “opt-out” available for update notifications.

If you do not want us to contact you, you may “opt-out” at any time. You may “opt-out” by contacting Customer Service Department of Freshsofts.com or by following the instructions included in the email correspondence.

**Our Web Site and Cookies**

Freshsofts.com utilizes visitor log files or cookies as well as hosted tracking with our website. The information collected with visitor cookies and through the hosted tracking is used to gain a better understanding of which sections of our site are most important to our users as well as identify possible navigation issues. This allows us to enhance your user experience in the future. The data collected from these visitor cookies and hosted tracking does not collect any personally identifiable information and is used in aggregate form only.

**Protecting Your Personal Information**

Where personal information is required, Freshsofts.com uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to transmit this data. This is done to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of the information you have offered. While Freshsofts.com strives to protect the personal information you submit to us, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. As such, Freshsofts.com cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our products and you do so at your own risk. Once your information has been received by Freshsofts.com, we will make our best effort to ensure the safety and security on our systems.

At times, Freshsofts.com may hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf. Such limited services include, but are not limited to, order fulfillment, direct mail services and answering customer questions about products and services. These companies will only be provided the information they need to perform the service, and they are strictly prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Freshsofts.com then you may contact us at  [_legalsoftstore@gmail.com_ _._](mailto:legalsoftstore@gmail.com)

[

Finally, while we will make every effort to preserve the privacy of our users, at times we may be required by law to disclose personal information.

](mailto:legalsoftstore@gmail.com)
